



To: Donald R Flory (Viewed)
May 10, 2023 at 02:31:00 AM
Message body:
Hello, this is a message about your upcoming appointment at Kaiser Permanente.

Donald has an appointment on 5/11/2023 at 11:30 AM

Check in now for this appointment from your list of upcoming appointments online or in our app.

ALEXANDER (M.D.) RIVERO (M.D.)

HEAD AND NECK SURGERY DEPT

OAKLAND MEDICAL CENTER-OAK

3600 Broadway OAKLAND CA 94611-0000

4th Floor
